Abby's many years of service required him to come up now. I appreciate it. What
is his son Michael now?
He's the vice president of analytics and portfolio management at PNC Financial.
Michael Kamana.
And he's also a speculative fiction author. The other is Pierre DeGionne.
Pierre is the publisher of Profile News, which is the largest Arabic English
newspaper in all of Ohio.
That's huge. He's also Abby's successor as president of Cameo and other groups.
It's my pleasure to introduce first, Pierre DeGionne.
I hope you're having a great time. I think we have a great lineup here tonight.
And I really want to thank the bottom of my heart, the Hansin family. Let's
give them a big hand of applause.
Thank you so much for what you do to the international community. Thank you so
much for this international hall of fame. You guys are a legendary in our
community and God bless you for being involved so much.
My name is Pierre DeGionne, as you have mentioned. And I am the president of
the Cleveland American Police Organization, known as Cameo.
And the chairman of the board of the American Lebanese Community Council and
the Lebanese Cultural Guard. Also, we are affiliated with the world Lebanese
Cultural Union.
I want to congratulate our dear friends inducted here tonight. They mean so
much to us. Judge of Purdue Junior, Rocky. Congratulations.
And Sheila Crawford, the president of the House of the Guard. Thank you for
what you've done.
What I'm going to do is to be here inducting you, the leader, the philanthropist
in the Lebanese community.
Abby, as we say in Arabic, Abdulla, Meena. Abby grew up in Kefraya, 11 in the
town located in the Bikar Valley. He was one of 10 siblings, came to the US in
1956, and issued a living in Richmond, Virginia, where he attended college.
And then, thank you to his lovely wife, Mona. She pursued him to relocate to Kefraya.
Thank you, Mona.
Abby is a clerk, not only to the Lebanese community, but to the whole of the
Eastern community.
There are not enough words to describe this Greek man. It will take me forever
to talk about him.
But I will alleviate as much as I can because I have to do it so. He's humble,
gentle, kind, a man of knowledge, help, peace, and constantly striving for
harmony in the community.
I have known Abby for over 30 years. My first meeting with him was in Kenya.
Abby was the longest serving president of Kenya, serving over 15 years.
He has remained very much involved as a board member and a parliamentarian. He
was also a former president of the Kirby Club.
It's an Lebanese club in northern Ohio. Abby remained active in our Lebanese
community, currently serving as a vice chairman and a board member of the
American Lebanese Community Council and the Lebanese Cultural Authority.
He is a devoted member of St Elias Milkeit Catholic Church, located in the
Brooklyn, where he served as a president of the council.
Abby recently retired from his weekly Arabic radio broadcasting show, which was
featured on WCSB for 21 years.
Abby has selfishly served the community for decades, helping hundreds of people
with immigration paperwork and translation services.
His involvement turns so deep into the community, as he has helped countless
people facilitate the process of coming to the US, finding them employment and
transforming people from the old country,
and assimilating them to life in the United States of America. He is a friend,
a mentor, and confident, not only to me, but to countless others.
Abby has been married to his wife Mona for 55 years. They have two children,
Michael and Sarah, and Dorothy, and three grandchildren.
Abby, you are one of the special select few in the Cleveland community to be
chosen as an inductee to the International Hall of Fame.
You are an example. We all strive to emulate. Congratulations on your induction.
I present you, Abby Wiener. Thank you.
Thank you.